hi i'm kyle green with the greenway
outdoors and today i'm going to talk to
you about the tracker targa v19 reason
why i'm making this video is because
when i was buying this boat and looking
into buying this boat i must have
watched 20 youtube videos that were all
terrible because i wanted to know every
detail about the boat but they were
either out of focus too close too far
away or didn't have the information i
cared about this is a huge purchase it's
like buying a house or a car and it's
something you're probably going to keep
for a long long time so let me show you
why this should be the boat for you
we'll start with the trailer because
we're outside of the water still it's
powder coated with galvashield which
basically is like a fancy way of saying
it's powder coated it's black it's
gritty and it keeps from chipping it
keeps them rusting and kind of protects
it so it doesn't look janky over time
you've got a full-size spare tire right
here the trailer is a custom fit tandem
axle and it's got an inside the frame
brake line system with one point bleed
and hydraulic drum brakes in both axles
coming around to the back you've got
some tie downs here this one didn't come
with it this is a little bit more of a
heavy duty one that i got myself to be
honest with you the first day the one
that came with it broke so they're just
kind of cheaper straps that come with it
so i'd get yourself some more heavy duty
ones and i mean it's holding your boat
on you want to protect it
the plug is a little bit lower than you
might have expected it's easy right now
because you see me doing it so obviously
you know where it goes but there's a lot
of holes back here and people make
mistakes especially with this one here
so make sure you go lower it's the one
down there
all right on the trailer here there is
like a step ladder with a big step on it
and this is the top step and then a big
pole that helps you get in and out of
the boat i took it off which is very
easy to do there's bolts to do it i took
it off because honestly i don't need it
i'm young and easy to
hop in quick but in addition to that the
pole was the tallest point of the boat
even taller than the window and i
couldn't fit it in my garage so when
you're pulling in like check for that
all right let's launch it
[Music]
with this boat
it gets out of the hole pretty quick
i've got the 150 horse on it
some people go bigger i mean you can do
the two
you know 200 225 but with the 150 on it
and with like two or three people i've
gotten up to 45 no problem so
yeah she gets on plane quick too
about two seconds flat and i'm on plane
sweet
smooth too
deep v
super deep v
makes everything just icy smooth
another cool addition
this grip right here you can put your
phone in there i've been going 40 with
that thing and it hasn't popped out yet
so you actually can trust it it's like a
trust build thing but it does work
really really well
you've got your master power your bilge
uh ford live well your back live well
and then the pump out features a horn
if you need it and then uh the cool
thing right here is the lighted uh live
wells so they light up at night and then
the nav system right there is for your
front and back lights when you've got
those plugged in but it's all off to the
side you can see good another thing is
they've got a bracket right here with
the cord so if you wanted to install
another big fish finder like that if
you're like a tournament bass fisherman
or something you can do that too all
right now that i've shown you all the
gauges and how to drive it let me show
you the storage in the front
all right first things first in the
front
you've got this movable front windshield
so it can bolt lock down
they call it a walk through front seat
here for fishing
now it folds up like this now if i sit
in it and it's locked in place and i
want to spin it i can make it so i can
spin around
lock it back down that way when you're
driving it's not doing one of those
deals and on top of that it's hydraulic
and you can move it to any of the other
post spots in the boat you just press
this button
pick it up move it out get it out of the
way now these pads up here are on the
fish and ski model which is the one that
we have and that's because we like to
take people out on the boat to hang out
you can ride up here talk about
comfortable and these are removable too
so it's just as simple as snapping them
down and snapping them back out so if
you're fishing and you want these mats
in the way you can take them out
going through the storage here this
cupboard here is where i keep my this is
my planner boards
and then i have four life vests in here
so literally it's big enough to fit four
light vests and the planter boards
and a lot of people use it for storage
of towels and things like that
but
i obviously use mine mostly for fishing
and then the one up here just in front
of it open that one up this is where i
keep my anchor so nice anchor bag anchor
in there works well for that
um
i think that's pretty much what everyone
uses it for i think that's pretty much
the anchor designated one
up here
is where our trolling motor is
so the cables and the setup for that and
i'll show you how that works in just one
second
and
last but not least our other live well
so we have another live well right here
as well
a couple secret compartments not too
many people realize
is right here and right here
honestly you can't keep much in them do
not keep anything in these when you're
driving down the road or if you plan on
being you know going really fast because
they do tend to open and close while
driving
i want to get some stronger magnets to
put on there but it works the same just
don't count on it on the expressway so
back to the trolling motor
this is a system foot pedal is going to
come standard with it it's a 70 pound
torque trolling motor which is pretty
strong to plug it in you just got this
right here
so it just plugs in nicely in there
and then you can do up or down for your
motor from up from back here too so if
you're coasting into some shallow water
or something you want to lift out your
main
motor you can do that there
and then to plug this in it's a little
finicky something i don't love but it
does work pretty good
is how to put the trolling motor on you
got to be really careful you've got this
little
little attachment here this is a female
end and then the male end
and
you got to put it in you got to make
sure all those prongs line up perfectly
if they don't you could break it and it
won't work so you do that screw it down
it's good to go
there's a tester on the top to check
your trolling motor and how it's doing
other than that it's just a standard
trolling motor 70 pounds of torque
foot pedal pretty easy to use i like it
and it does have a continuous setting so
if you want to be going in a constant
direction you can set that up too
and while we're talking about plugs to
charge the boat you don't need a trickle
charger anymore i have three batteries
hooked up to this boat and it's just a
standard 115 volt outlet that you plug
it into in the wall and
honestly it it holds a charge really
well i'll charge it full and then i've
gone out and used the trolling motor on
the detroit river for like eight hours
two days in a row and on the third day
it was still completely fine so i
haven't run it out yet but i'm not gonna
keep risking it i'll plug it in every
night
all right walking back through this is
uh the main rod locker
now right now i've got four rods in
there with line counting reels all
rigged up with cabela's rapala tight
bluers keep in mind i got four in there
and there's still plenty of room for at
least another four so a lot of room in
that rod store it's super nice there's a
little compartment underneath there too
that i keep my line in so like if i need
to re-spool it i keep it in that little
tiny compartment there that's up
underneath the lures
and that just locks like that
then right here
this storage this is where we keep our
ski rope
and then
there's more storage underneath there
where we keep a bunch of life jackets
and that's also where the batteries are
at too keep in mind when you're putting
stuff in there that you don't want to be
like rattling the batteries around you
know what i mean so i keep it in there
but i make sure that the jackets stay
well away from
the battery ports in there
kind of nice
it's dry storage too it doesn't get wet
underneath here
a little compartment there i keep my
lines in there right now we're in the
water so the lines that are on the side
of the boat where we dock are already in
there
and then there's an identical one on
that side that one's just where i keep
all my fire extinguishers my lighting
kits and then also all the paperwork for
the boat itself and then
waterproof compartment here
cell phones phones all kinds really big
and
it does lock so if you're going into a
gas station or something like that you
want to keep all your stuff safe because
i keep my wall in there that's nice too
and now locker storage in both gunnels
on both sides it's got three rod holders
but you could put two in depending on
the size of the rod for each but minimum
three works pretty good it also locks
like i said if you're in the gas station
or something like that it works well and
as you see behind me here i haven't
really mentioned it yet but i have a 9.9
kicker motor it's optional so that
doesn't come standard with the package
but when you get that added on it
actually runs off the exact same fuel
tank as your main motor does but it does
have its own throttle shifter key
everything like that on the side here so
you actually have two when you have that
works great just one more thing i wanted
you to know all right next thing we'll
talk about is the versatrack system so
this is
superior to basically all other rod
holder system but the key to it is to
know this you cannot buy these
aftermarket rod holders as of right now
in the store you actually have to go to
the tracker boats facility and actually
ask them to buy it or special order it
there because if you just buy rod
holders on the internet it will not be
the right ones i promise you but the way
the versatrax system works is it goes
right along the gunnel here and it makes
it so that you can move
your rod holders anyway anywhere you
want you just unscrew them move it
tighten it down and you're good to go
it's really really nice in order to get
them off you just slide them out the
back there's a little hole and you just
pop it out of there no big deal the
system's awesome just make sure you look
into where you're buying the rod holders
from because you'll probably get the
wrong ones if you don't actually talk to
your tracker people to get them so then
that brings us to the back seats
super cool this folds down
and
that snaps on
then this can fold over so now you have
more fishable platform and just like the
front seat these posts all these places
are where you can insert the other seats
that you have there the boat will come
with four seats total plus the back two
jumper seats i take a lot of them out
because they honestly get in the way and
i like more open space but this is super
nice because you can do the same thing
with this deal
move that over and bam look at you
you've got all this fishable space put a
seat here you're good to go now there's
also as you may have guessed more
storage so right here
this storage is what i use as my tackle
box and you can see i've got everything
organized in there it uh it's got a
plastic shell on the inside to keep
everything kind of you know if you put
wet stuff in there it's not a big big
deal a lot of people keep their towels
in there but we're using this boat for
fishing so you can imagine what's going
to go in there back here this is
actually going to be where your other
battery is so that's just right there
it's your crank battery
but keep in mind that 115 volt outlet
charges this one and the trolling motor
batteries which will be found in the
middle of the boat this one right here
is your live well
it's very very big it's got a bait
bucket built in it's got a light right
there that can turn on at night so you
can see what's going on in the live well
so you don't get bit by a pike happened
to our buddy scott once
we didn't have this boat then
back here another little dry storage
it's where i keep all of the uh
additives that i have to put in the
motor so i use
stabil every single time i fill up
and then i also use quick clean every
two times and
those two supplements added your fuel
are what are actually being your mercury
manual so make sure that you're doing
that one more little piece of storage is
right here this is where i keep my
bumpers so at the docks uh bass pro
makes these really cool inflatable
bumpers you just unscrew this unstrap
them and then they blow up but then they
fold down so you don't have those big
ugly buoys taking up all the room in the
boat they fold up nice you wouldn't even
know they're there
and then if you got a lot of people you
want to pop these back up
you're gonna sit down again so
pretty cool right here
we've got storage on the sidewall so
this is where we keep our fishing nut
this is another um
another cool product by bass pro first
let's get this ski tow piling out so if
you get the fishing ski model it's going
to come with the
skeeto pi one right there you just
unscrew the little bracket that's in
there and screw this in and that'll work
perfectly for you it just screws right
in keep in mind a lot of people don't
know this the ski tow pylon is not meant
for tubing do not use it for tubing
there's a weight limit on it it's only
meant to be used for skiing you could
break the boat doing it otherwise
then uh this fishing net another option
from bass pro
i love this it's got this rubber part on
the front our producer ryan actually
uses this to catch timberdoodle so that
he doesn't hurt them but um because
without that front bar because a lot of
times when you swat them you can hurt
them but this way this can fold down
break up
it's like nothing takes up no room slide
it in there i also keep my ore and my
lights in there as well
so that everything's kind of covered and
good to go
that is the track of target v19 for 2021
it's amazing one of the things i wanted
to note that i didn't hit on through the
walkthrough is the uh the metal that
they use to build the boat it's so much
thicker than almost any other boat
and because of that
the ride is so smooth it makes such a
big difference having that big over
exaggerated deep v with that big heavy
metal really cuts through the waves and
that's why i like it the most take it
out skiing take it out fishing enjoy i'm
kyle green stay green
[Music]
you